<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>My City RSS Feed</title><link>http://localhost:8888/rss_feed.xml</link><description>RSS feed for cities and places of interest</description><item><title>London</title><description>Population: 8900000, Country: United Kingdom</description><weather>Temperature: 18.2 °C, Description: scattered clouds, Humidity: 47%, Wind Speed: 6.17 m/s</weather><place><name>The British Museum</name><type>Museum</type><description>"The British Museum is a museum dedicated to human history, art, and culture.The British Museum is unique in bringing together under one roof the cultures of the world, spanning continents and oceans."</description></place><place><name>Buckingham Palace</name><type>Palace</type><description>Buckingham Palace is the London residence and administrative headquarters of the monarch of the United Kingdom. Buckingham Palace has 775 rooms. These include 19 State rooms, 52 Royal and guest bedrooms, 188 staff bedrooms, 92 offices and 78 bathrooms. In measurements, the building is 108 metres long across the front, 120 metres deep (including the central quadrangle) and 24 metres high.</description></place><place><name>Tower of London</name><type>Historical Site</type><description>Historic castle and prison with tours. As the most secure castle in the land, the Tower guarded royal possessions and even the royal family in times of war and rebellion. But for 500 years monarchs also used the Tower as a surprisingly luxurious palace. Throughout history, the Tower has also been a visible symbol of awe and fear.</description></place><place><name>London Eye</name><type>Tourist Attraction</type><description>Ferris wheel with panoramic views. At 135m, The London Eye is the world's largest cantilevered observation wheel. It was conceived and designed by Marks Barfield Architects and was launched in 2000. It has won over 85 awards for national and international tourism, outstanding architectural quality and engineering achievement</description></place><place><name>Westminster Abbey</name><type>Historical Site</type><description>Historic church with coronations</description></place><place><name>Tate Modern</name><type>Art Museum</type><description>Contemporary art museum in former power station</description></place></item><item><title>New York City</title><description>Population: 8400000, Country: United States</description><weather>Temperature: 21.37 °C, Description: overcast clouds, Humidity: 74%, Wind Speed: 3.6 m/s</weather><place><name>Central Park</name><type>Park</type><description>Central Park is an urban park in New York City located between the Upper West and Upper East Sides of Manhattan. Central Park is full of attractions, from green meadows to sprawling waters, gardens and unique bridges, music and performance centres, educational facilities, classical architecture and more. Its picturesque beauty boasts natural green landscapes and vistas as far as the eye can see.</description></place><place><name>Statue of Liberty</name><type>Monument</type><description>The Statue of Liberty stands in Upper New York Bay, a universal symbol of freedom. Originally conceived as an emblem of the friendship between the people of France and the U.S. and a sign of their mutual desire for liberty, it was also meant to celebrate the abolition of slavery following the U.S. Civil War.</description></place><place><name>Times Square</name><type>Landmark</type><description>Times Square is a major commercial and entertainment hub in New York City. Together with adjacent Duffy Square, Times Square is a bowtie-shaped plaza five blocks long between 42nd and 47th Streets. Times Square is brightly lit by numerous digital billboards and advertisements as well as businesses offering 24/7 service.</description></place><place><name>Empire State Building</name><type>Skyscraper</type><description>Iconic skyscraper with observatories. At its top floor, the Empire State Building stands 1,250 feet (380 meters) tall. Counting the spire and antenna, the building clocks in at a mighty 1,454 feet (443 meters). It's currently the 4th tallest building in New York City, the 6th tallest in the United States, and the 43rd tallest tower in the world.</description></place><place><name>Brooklyn Bridge</name><type>Bridge</type><description>Iconic bridge connecting Manhattan and Brooklyn</description></place><place><name>Metropolitan Museum of Art</name><type>Art Museum</type><description>Major art museum with vast collections</description></place></item></channel></rss>